whitecoatinvestor.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy For The White Coat Investor | The White Coat Investor - Investing And Personal Finance Information For Physicians, Dentists, Residents, Students, And Other Highly-Educated Busy Professionals

> _The privacy of our visitors to http://whitecoatinvestor.com is important to us.   This website recognizes that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit http://whitecoatinvestor.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties._
> 
> **_Log Files_**  
>  _As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.   The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site._
> 
> **_Cookies and Web Beacons_**  
>  _We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.   This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums._
> 
> **_Advertisements_**  
>  _We also use third party advertisements on The White Coat Investor to support our site.   Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites)._
> 
> **_How to Opt Out_**  
>  _You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.   However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts._
> 
> _AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by[JenSense](http://www.jensense.com/)_
